[{"answer": "He wanted to have it restrung.  Here I need to pick that u", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Switch.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Oh, Hi", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "O", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Switch.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Oh, you'll be playing ..", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "My doctor said it might never fully heal. I may never play again", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Switch.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "If I can't play tennis I don't know what I'll do", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "If I can't play tennis I don't know what I'll do", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Switch.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You don't know how lucky you are to be healthy ..", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Well, why don't you wait 'til she's not there on her lunch hour and just take it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Switch.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Stealing? You loaned her the racquet", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "that plac", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Switch.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "that plac", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "JERR", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Switch.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "JERR", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "It was a great sounding laugh too, kind of lilting and feminin", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Switch.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Yeah", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Can't be done, huh", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Switch.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "\"The Switch", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I wonder", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Switch.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "They didn't have roommates in the Middle Ages", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Leave ..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Switch.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I don't have to but I will. Street Babs and my frien", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Hi Mr. my frien", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Switch.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Ah couldn't be better. Hi my friend", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Hi Cosm", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Switch.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Hi Mrs. my frien", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "You ma, know I've been thinking. I want you to quit that matron job", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Switch.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Well maybe we could go into business together. If you're clean", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Uh, yeah. Do you know my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Switch.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "my friend left", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Do you ever just get down on your knees and thank god that you know me and have access to my dementia", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Switch.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "You're not goin to do it? What do you mean, You're not goin to do it", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Hey, what happened? Did you get your racquet", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Switch.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "What do you mean you got caught", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "No, I got caught", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Switch.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Her assistant caught me. And now I'm probably not going to get a job. He's going to tell my friend that I was sneakin around her office", "qsentId": 36}]